In the end, all the dreams of a man
Of course, you and I will always be with you
That's right, that's right, that's right
I'll always be with you in the future
So you're happy, so don't be with me
I'll always be with you
There's a smile on your lips
You and you, you and you
If you love me, if you love me,
I'll be with you for the rest of my life
I don't want to be with you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Hello, hello
It's time machine
Look, this is it
It's not good, it's good
Hey, you said you'd buy it for your parents
You're not good at it
I'm not good at it
This is it
Sorry
Is it okay?
I'm not good at it!
You're not good at it!
Stop it
I love you
You have a good life for your parents
Do you always say that to me?
Do you?
That's right, do you?
Yes, do you?
If you give me a gift, I'm fine
But can't you give me a gift?
I don't give a gift to you
Then now you're free
I've been in the research department
I'm not good at it at all
That's right
That was the last time
I was back in the morning
I've been waiting for you for a long time
What are you saying?
Your dad said something was really popular
I think it's better to wear it the same way
Like the first impression
Yes, maybe it's going to be a third month
I don't want you to be angry with me.
If you don't come out early, I'll be in trouble.
I'm not jealous of you.
In front of me is Yukigumo Seizouki.
In front of me is Hoya-ki, who can talk to animals.
In front of me is...
What is that?
A man will become a woman.
That's right. Everyone was a failure.
It's not good. There's a dream.
But...
Your mother was pregnant, too.
Ah! She was pregnant!
She was pregnant today, too.
I'm thinking about something like this.
Your mother is quite tired.
I don't think I can use that.
But it's been a while.
Look.
What are you doing this time?
You know what I'm doing, don't you?
I want to go to the bathroom, too.
What?
Hmm?
What is it?
Yeah.
I heard it from the doctor before.
You heard it?
Is it a Thai machine?
No, it's a lie, isn't it?
Maybe...
The doctor is real.
He's making a real Thai machine.
It's amazing!
If you do that, you can go anywhere you want.
If you do that...
I'll do it!
Neato-san!
Hey, hey!
You're making a real Thai machine, aren't you?
Then, let me tell you.
I made a lot of money, right?
Ah-san, what do you mean?
That's not true.
Then, you don't have to eat like last night.
It's a Thai machine.
Let's go!
Here, here.
Don't go too far.
Wait for me.
Senta, what are you doing?
Oh, it's raining.
What's wrong?
I made a Thai machine.
Thai machine?
It's still there.
I'm not sure if I can do it for you, but I'll give you a chance to do it.
It's a Thai machine.
Really?
I'm not saying it to others.
If I do it for the past, I'll get angry.
So, I can't do it?
No, no.
I don't want to go to the emergency room.
But, just a little.
I want to see a Thai machine.
Where?
Hey, where are you?
It's snowing.
Oh, stop it.
If you get angry, I won't do it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's what it is.
You can do that too, right?
Yeah.
It's because it's a dog's body.
Let's go.
I'll be right back.
It's snowing.
Oh, yeah.
Ate-san.
I had a lot of fun since I was little.
I had a lot of work to do.
I learned a lot of things.
Me too.
I did a lot of things with Beiguma.
I knew it better than I thought.
Me too.
I was born when I was in a TV game.
It's amazing, right?
I know what I'm talking about.
I can do anything.
So, I'm a Thai machine.
Yeah.
I'll try my best.
I think it's because I'm nervous.
I thought I was doing it.
If I don't sleep in the bathroom,
I think it's because I'm a little nervous.
Yeah.
Hey, I thought I'd be home when I got home.
What?
You're going to sleep in the bathroom, aren't you?
No, I'm not going to sleep in the bathroom with you.
Yo-chan!
You said you'd only eat lunch with Hachuru, right?
Why?
Huh?
Oh, my.
I'm not going to sleep again.
I'm going to sleep in the bathroom for a while.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Huh?
Have you lost your mind?
Honey is not going to sleep!
Ehh.....
Dani-chan....
LOL
This is so rich...
I want to dye my hair so I can give you some sunshine
Hiya!
Let's go!
Hey!
If you're a dog, you won't be able to walk away.
I'm a dog, so I'm a virgin.
Huh?
It's not a dog.
Where did you come from?
Eh?
From the morning?
That's right.
I didn't come back in time.
What did you think?
Where did you go?
You.
Now!
I don't want to have dinner with you.
Ah!
Are you going to take a walk with me today?
I haven't.
Today, Hazuki and her mother are going to take a walk.
No!
Oh!
I knew it!
Now, let's go!
Huh?
It's strange!
What's going on?
Honey!
Please let me know if you like it.
Ah!
Hurry up!
Huh?
Are you going to the other side?
I just went there.
Didn't you go to the second floor?
Hmm...
Huh?
Wait!
There it is!
Hey! Where are you going?
Okay!
It's the beginning of the treatment.
That's right!
I knew you would come to the other side,
so I'll be right back.
I knew it!
Huh?
Where are you going?
What are you going to do?
Really?
Wait!
It's true!
Time machine is completed!
It's hard!
Toku!
It's true!
Time machine is completed!
Yeah!
It was a success at the Shiyun store!
Really!
It's true!
Wow!
I'm so excited to see you again!
Yeah!
It's so difficult!
I'm going to play a game now!
Yeah!
It's a big event for Takamaya Shoten.
Everyone, please give me a match!
Yeah!
Everyone, let's play!
I'm going to play!
Everyone, look!
I'm going to play a game from where I'm going to play.
I'll be in my place from now on.
I'm going to play a game!
It's a game!
Taku you're Margaret's brother.
I'mフロに入らないんで
I have to get comments from Yukari.
But it's going well.
It's an episode of the Holiday No Coral in stone.
It's got to be a TV Assassins.
It sounds cool, isn't it?
Oh!
I'm such a waste of time.
That's right!
You said that right?
Yeah, that's great.
You're going to be in the middle of the university, right?
Daiko?
Me?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm going to be in the middle of the university.
I saw a lot of fun.
What?
Fun?
I'm going to be in the middle of the university.
I just want to know what you've been doing in the red ribbon.
Really?
Huh? What's wrong?
Did you get hurt?
Huh?
What the hell is this?
After all, I've seen a lot of fun.
What about Muka Muka?
Muka Muka?
When Muka Muka came back from the town of Ueba,
he came back from the town of Tamago.
He came to hide in the time machine.
That's a lie!
What?
What's wrong?
That's right.
What?
What the hell are you doing?
I just thought you were going to be like this.
I'm so sorry.
I guess I saw that guy in the morning.
I'm not feeling well.
I don't care.
I haven't been in the time machine yet.
That's right.
I'm going to be in the middle of the university.
There were things like this.
The adults were all children.
But the adults who remember those things
don't have a future.
What do you think?
I don't think the adults have a future.
That's right.
I'm going to be in the middle of the university.
I love you.
Thank you.
5 seconds.
4 seconds.
I saw something.
What happened?
The US military office.
Yes.
Where was the US military office?
What was that?
Mrs. Muka hadзаo.
V access.
She got back!
This is impossible!
Oh!
Stop it, Muka.
Where am I going?
Let's go.
Huh?
I didn't know that I bought this chest from Africa,
but the black seal was gone!
It's been 30 years.
What? What's that?
Maybe 30 years ago,
I came back to this seal.
Sanutari!
I did it!
I was going to get a time machine!
Wow!
I'm going to get a time machine!
I'm coming!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Yeah!
I think we're going to start with something else again.
It's not like this.
But...
I'm looking forward to it, right?
Hm?
Well...
We're going to do it, too.
Let's do it!
Who's got the camera on?
Why are you so scared?
Oh, well...
What shall we do?
I don't know.
Why are you so scared?
We'll have to see, too.
Let's just do things that we can do.
I wonder what we're going to do.
Have you said you love me?
Yeah!
But we're going to the spark.
We're going to fix our time machine.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Translated by Releska
Ato-o-o yo nori nori no ii aidi-o-iru no
Tokikou e toki o cole koko-ai-kite-iru heng-eng-na-yatsu
I'll give you a time when you say something
There's a way to improve me
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you
That's why I'm here to enjoy our time
We have a history of history
Guys, everyone, please watch the movie
The main character of the movie is Tsume Kaku and the father of the big brother
The big brother of the big brother was very close
The baby face of the old brother of the baby face!
Oh, okay!
Good job!
Yeah, good job!
Ah, this is so good!
Next episode, Mugamu Kaparanai.
Jokicjokic, Kyoryu.
See you again in the next episode.